声明：本字幕由YYeTs人人影视字幕组原创翻译制作
禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎登录人人影视论坛交流 下载 在线观看 www.YYeTs.net
■
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：66 paradise 小帝 susan
校对：互校 美景时间轴：YY吕伟 leolou squllroina
========== 字幕总监制：何何   ==========
能听到我吗?
Can you hear me?
你还好吗?
You okay?
我只是想知道为什么
Come on! come on! I just wanna know why.
发生什么了?
What happened?
他在瞒着我们!
He knows somethin'!
-我想知道真相! -我不知道  这就是真相
I want the truth! I don't know. that's the truth.
-我跟你说  我不知道为什么  不过现在没有信号 -信号?
I'm telling you, I don't know why, but there's no signal now. signal?
-什么  你昨晚呼叫他们的时候还有信号的 -是的
What, there was a signal when you called them last night. that's right.
那那那什么?  现在他们不理我们了吗?
So--so--so what? now they're just ignoring us?
那我们怎么知道他们为什么不回应我们?
How are we supposed to know why they're not answering?
-又没在跟你说话  -可能你现在还没发觉
Oh, who's talking to you? and in case you haven't noticed,
我们不在那该死的船上  是吧? -你说话注意点  Red
We're not on the bloody boat, are we? just watch your tone, red.
我只是想知道为什么
I just wanna know why. hey!
-大家都需要冷静下  好吗? -Jack
Everybody just needs to calm down, okay? jack,
这些人在骗我们
These people are lying to us.
我知道他们在说谎  我知道
I know they're lying. I know it.
他们的人迟早要回来接他们的
Sooner or later, their people are gonna come back for them,
我们就等着他们来好了
And when they do, we'll be waiting for them.
-要是他们又逃跑呢? -听我说
Unless they run off again. listen to me.
-Jack  你还好吗? -我很好
Jack, are you all right? no, I'm fine.
我们要耐心点  好吗?
We just have to be patient, okay?
我已经把大家带到了这一步
I've gotten us this far.
我说过我会让大家都离开这个岛的  所有人
I said I was gonna get us off the island--all of us.
我承诺过我会的
I promised that I would.
Jack?  Jack?  Jack?
Jack? jack? jack?
Jack
Jack.
喂?
Hello?
Shephard医生?
Dr. shephard?
只是确认下十一点你和Berenberg先生的会谈
Just confirming your 11:00 consult with ms. berenberg.
昨天已经把它提前了
It was moved up yesterday,
我知道你对老记不住你的日程
And I know how you are with your calendar.
知道了  我记得的  Jane  我会...我会去的
Yeah. yeah, I remember, jane. I'll, um... I'll be in there.
谢谢你  医生  好的  拜拜
Thank you, doctor. all right. bye.
妈的
Ow. son of a bitch.
你也早安
Morning yourself.
我给你买了个剃须刀
I bought you a razor.
什么  你不喜欢胡渣吗?
What, you don't like the scruff?
剃须刀就在水池那  Jack
Razor's by the sink, jack.
早安
Morning.
"Alice拿起扇子  因为大厅里很热"
"alice took up the fan, and as the hall was very hot,
"她一直不停地扇着扇子
"she kept fanning herself
"继续说着
"all the time she went on talking,
"亲爱的亲爱的  今天的一切怎么都那么奇怪啊
"'dear, dear. how queer everything is today.
"昨天  一切都是正常的
"'and yesterday, things went on just as usual.
"我想知道我是否在黑夜中已经改变
"'i wonder if I've been changed in the night.
让我想想  今早醒来时还是那个原来那个样子吗?
Let me think. was I the same when I got up this morning?'"
"可是如果我不是原来的我  那接下来的问题是
"'but if I'm not the same, the next question is,
"那么我到底是谁?
"who in the world am i?'
那真是个难题啊"
Aha, that's the great puzzle."
天生当爸爸的料啊
You're a natural.
是吗?
Yeah?
我父亲曾经给我说过这个故事
My old man used to read me that story.
真的吗?
Really?
能听到你说你赞美你爸爸的话真是感动
It's just sweet hearing you say nice things about your dad.
我总不说我爸爸的好话吗?
I don't say nice things about my dad?
我得说他讲故事很棒
Well, he was a good storyteller. I'll give him that.
你还好吗?
You okay?
只是  我...我喜爱看到你和他
Just, i... I love seeing you with him.
我很高兴你改变了你的想法
I'm so glad you changed your mind.
我很高兴你在这儿
I'm so glad that you're here.
我也是
Me, too.
让他待在阴凉处  我去拿点水给他
Keep him in the shade. I'll get him some water.
别靠太近  大家
Give--give him some air, guys.
好
Yeah.
我很好  我很好  我很好
I'm fine. I'm good. I'm good.
-怎么了? -他晕过去了
Hey, what happened? he passed out.
你晕过去了?
You fainted?
我很好  我只是...只是有点脱水
I'm fine. I'm just, uh... just a little dehydrated.
不是  Jack  你不好  你在发烧
No, jack. you're not okay. you're burning up.
我很好  我很好  我只是...
I'm fine. I'm fine. I just...
-只是需要休息一会儿 -Jack
Just need to get a little rest. jack--
-还好吧? -恩  只是有点虚弱
You okay? yeah, just a bit woozy.
好多了  只是还有点疼
It's better. bit of a headache,
不过至少我再看不见"脏东西"了
But at least I'm not seeing things anymore.
是吗?  你看到什么了?
Yeah? what'd you see?
走你的路  Donger
Back off, donger.
-我只是找点话题 -省省吧
I'm just making conversation. let's make some time.
今晚扎营之前我想多赶点路
I wanna cover more ground before we gotta camp tonight.
如果我们快点  明天中午就能到海边了
If we hoof it, we can make it to the beach by noon tomorrow.
不要!
No!
什么?
What?
Danielle和Karl是谁?
Who's danielle and karl?
你是说Rousseau?  那个法国女人?
Y-you mean rousseau? the french woman?
天啊
Oh, my god.
Karl
Karl.
你怎么知道他们被埋在那里的?
How'd you know they were down there?
你的兄弟干的?
Your buddies do this?
他们不是我的兄弟
They're not my buddies, man.
我不是被雇佣来做这个的
I didn't sign up for this.
我们能不能离开这里?  我们可以走吗?
Can we just--can we just get out of here, please? can we just go?
好的好的  当然要走  不过别急
Yeah, yeah, of course. but don't worry.
我们一旦回到海边  一切就会没事了
Once we get back to the beach, everything's gonna be fine.
好吗?
All right?
我真讨厌生病
I hate being sick.
你觉得是什么病?
What do you think it is?
是食物中毒
It's food poisoning.
什么让你觉得是那个?
What makes you think that?
我有点绞痛  脱水  恶心
I've got some cramping, dehydrated, nausea.
我保留意见
I respectfully disagree.
你敢掀起你的衬衫吗?
You want to lift your shirt up?
如果是食物中毒  你就根本没有什么可害怕的
If it's food poisoning, you got nothing to worry about.
是你的阑尾  Jack
It's your appendix, jack.
什么时候开始痛的?
When did the pain start?
昨天
Yesterday.
已经疝气了吗?
Has it ruptured?
还没有
Not yet.
那么...
Well...
我想我们要把它取出来
I guess we're just gonna have to take it out.
你记得医疗救护站在哪?
Do you remember where the medical station is?
-是吗  -是的  我知道
-Or don't you? -Yes, I remember.
我需要你带这些器具回来
These are the instruments that I need you to bring back.
-在检验室的抽屉里能找到  -夹子?  线?
-You'll find them in the drawers in the exam room. -"clamps"? sutures"?
Juliet  我不认得这些东西
Juliet, I don't know what these look like.
我可以帮助你  我熟悉手术器具
I can help you. I'm familiar with surgical instruments.
-我还以为你只是个物理学家  -是的
I thought you were a physicist. Yeah, well,
我以前也做过动物尸体解剖  因此...
I've done some animal autopsies, too, so if--if-- no.
-我们不能相信他们  -瞧  Dan  我早跟你说过
We can't trust them. -See, Dan? I told you.
他们早已认定我们会杀害他们
They're convinced we're trying to kill 'em.
-最好别去插手  -该死的  Charlotte
-Might as well keep playing the part. -Damn it, charlotte.
就是因为这样  就因为这样
That right there, that right there.
你的态度  你糟糕的态度
Your--your attitude-- your very bad attitude--
正是这样他们才不信任我们
It's exactly why they don't trust us.
别这样了
Come on.
Juliet  求你
Juliet, please.
不要把这些事  所发生的一切都怪罪在我们头上
Don't blame us for--for this, for whatever is happening.
我们是科学家  我们不想任何人受到伤害
We're scientists. We don't want anyone to get hurt.
我们只想帮忙  求你让我们去
We just wanna help. Please let us help.
只要有他们一个企图逃跑  就朝他们的腿开枪
Either of them tries to run? Shoot 'em in the leg.
尽快赶回来  好吗
Get back here as fast as you can. Okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
我需要一块干净的地方
We need to create a sterile environment.
找一块硬地  洗干净
Find a hard surface, wash it down,
尽量找到更多的防水布
Gather as many tarps as you can.
嘿  Juliet
Hey, juliet.
如果医疗救护站有我们需要的任何东西
If everything that we need is at the medical station,
-那我们为何不把Jack直接带到那去  -因为如果我们移动他
-Then why don't we just bring jack there? -Because if we move him,
他的阑尾可能就因此破裂
There's a good chance that his appendix will rupture.
还有如果真这样了  他就会死
And if that happens, he's gonna die.
想都别想
Don't even think about it.
什么
What?
不准看她  不准和她说话
Don't look at her. Don't talk to her.
不准打扰她
Don't mess with her.
给你下禁令  离她20英尺远
You got a restraining order. 20 feet.
你是谁  她大哥哥?
What are you, her big brother?
不是  我是要狠狠揍你的人
No. I'm the guy who's gonna put a boot in your face
除非你说  是的  我知道了
Unless you say, "yeah. I getcha."
是的  我知道了
Yeah. I getcha.
亲爱的  我相信Jack不会有事的
Honey, I am sure Jack is gonna be okay.
阑尾切除术
An appendectomy
是一种最常见的手术
Is just about the most common kind of surgery there is.
我不是在想这个
That's not what I was thinking about.
我在想  他怎么就生病了
I was thinking, "why did he get sick?"
怎么?  只是  只是运气不好罢了
Why? It's just-- it's just bad luck.
就在我们都以为要获救的时候
The day before we're all supposed to be rescued,
我们最依赖的人
The person that we count on the most
却突然陷入了生命危险
Suddenly comes down with a life-threatening condition,
-而你却把这归因于运气不好?  -那你是说
-And you're chalking it up to bad luck? -Well, what are you saying,
难道Jack做了一些冒犯上帝的事
That--that Jack did something to offend the gods?
-人们生病了  Rose  -不是在这
People get sick, Rose. -Not here.
在这里  他们都更好了
Here, they get better.
你最后一次这样做是什么时候
When was the last time you did this?
你说的是阑尾切除术还是给男人刮肚子?
An appendectomy or shaving a man's stomach?
在我的住处
In my residency.
我做过很多这样的手术
I did a lot of 'em back then.
那你应该知道切口在
Then you know the incision needs to be
你刮的地方往下2英寸
2 inches lower than where you're shaving.
我只是在清洗这块
I'm just cleaning the area.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我想跟你谈谈
I wanna talk you through it.
什么?
What?
我不想失去意识
I don't want to be unconscious.
我们可以用利多卡因(一种局部麻醉剂)
We can use the lidocaine
这样我就能看到手术过程
And then I can watch the procedure,
帮助你
Help you out.
你躺平了我手又在腹腔
And, uh, how are you gonna watch
你怎么能够看到
Flat on your back with my hand in your abdominal cavity?
我们可以用镜子  Kate来拿
We can use a mirror. kate can hold it.
如果需要人的话
If someone's going to be in there,
难道不应该是有手术经验的人吗?
Shouldn't it be someone with medical experience?
-Bernard医生  -不  我希望Kate在这
-Bernard's a dentist-- -No, I want it to be kate.
别担心  Berenberg小姐  你的状态很好
Don't worry, Ms. berenberg. You're in good hands.
-那明天早上5点见  -好的
-I'll see you tomorrow at 5:00 a.m.? -Mm-hmm.
记住  不要吃太硬的食物  好吗
And remember, no solid food. okay?
-谢谢  医生  -祝你晚上愉快
-Thank you, doctor. -Have a good evening.
你看一下这张X射线图?
Will you take a look at this x-ray?
是14号的  我想知道你的看法  L4号  好的
-Uh, it's in the L4. I wanna know what you think. -The L4. yeah. yeah.
Shephard医生  有你的电话
Oh, Dr. Shephard, there's a call for you.
是Stillman从Santa rosa医院打来的
It's a dr. stillman from Santa rosa hospital,
说是有关你一个朋友的
Says it's about a friend of yours.
他拒绝服药
He's refusing to take his meds,
还不肯睡觉
And he's stopped sleeping.
他的治疗方案进展如何?
What about his therapy sessions?
治疗毫无效果
Therapy's... been rendered useless.
为何会这样呢?
And why is that?
因为他认为我不存在
Because he doesn't think I exist.
你为什么不吃药呢
Why aren't you taking your meds?
因为我们快死了
Cause we're dead...
我们所有人
All of us.
大洋航班六人  都要死了
All the oceanic six-- we're all dead.
我们从未离开过那岛
We never got off that island.
Hurley
Hurley...
不是那样的
That is not true.
我今天干了什么
What did I do today?
我...
I, uh...
起床后  洗了个澡
I woke up, took a shower.
我和Kate一起喂孩子吃饭
Uh, kate and I fed the baby.
我还以为你不想和Aaron扯上关系
I thought you didn't want anything to do with aaron.
审讯过后我改变注意了
I changed my mind after the trial.
和Kate生活在一起
Living with kate...
照顾Aaron
Taking care of aaron...
一切都那么幸福完美
It all seems so perfect...
就像是在天堂
Just like heaven.
不能因为我很幸福
Just because I'm happy
就说这不是真的  Hurley
Doesn't mean that this isn't real, hurley.
不管怎样  我也曾经幸福过  Jack
I was happy, too, jack...
虽然只有那么一会儿
For a while, anyway.
后来我遇见了Charlie
Then I saw charlie.
他喜欢和我一起坐在长椅上
He likes to sit with me on the bench
坐在草坪上
Out on the front lawn.
真的很酷
It's pretty cool, actually.
很好啊  那么你们俩都说些什么呢
Okay.  so what do the two of you talk about?
昨天他告诉我你要来看我
Well, yesterday, he told me you were gonna be coming by.
他叫我给你捎个信
He wanted me to give you a message.
他叫我写下来了  这样我就不会搞砸
He made me write it down so I wouldn't mess it up.
"你不该抚养他  Jack"
"you're not supposed to raise him, jack."
这消息有什么意思吗?
Does that make any sense?
不  这...毫无道理
No, that... doesn't make any sense.
你认为他说的是Aaron吗?
Do you think he means aaron?
吃药  Hurley
Take your meds, hurley.
嘿  Jack
Hey, jack?
Charlie还说有人会去拜访你
Charlie said someone's gonna be visiting you, too.
很快
Soon.
我们到了
We're here.
我先进去好吗
Why don't you let me go first?
你知道的  安全第一
Um, you know, make sure everything's safe.
小心点  Dan
Be careful, dan.
好的
Absolutely.
她知道他喜欢她吗
Do you think she knows he likes her?
她是个女人  知道的
She's a woman. She knows.
Jin 走吧
Jin. Come on.
你认为这电是哪来的
Where do you suppose all this power's coming from?
把这个记下来  Dan
Add that one to the list, dan.
我们去搬设备  然后走人  好吗
Let's just grab the equipment and go, shall we?
你没事吧?
Are you all right?
Juliet就是把我带在这的
This is where Juliet brought me.
我们的孩子当时就在这里
This is where I saw our baby.
他们没打算帮助我们  Jin
They're not going to help us, Jin.
不用担心他们
Don't worry about them.
我向你保证  Sun
I promise you Sun.
我会带你和孩子离开这岛的
I will get you and our baby off this island.
需要我抱一会儿孩子吗?
Whoa! hey, you want a hand with the baby?
不用  谢谢  我很好
Oh, no, thanks. I'm fine.
-真的吗  我和孩子很合得来  -对于禁令
You sure? I'm good with kids. what part of "restraining order"
你还有不明白的吗?
Don't you understand?
站到我后面  Claire
Get behind me, claire.
-Lapidus?  -Miles?
Lapidus? miles?
你们认识?
You two know each other?
-你们得藏起来  伙计  马上  -什么
You gotta hide, man, right now. what?
Keamy回来了
Keamy's coming back,
如果被发现  他会把你们杀光的
And if he sees you, he'll kill all of ya.
他快到了  伙计们  马上藏起来!
And he's close, man. you gotta hide now!
快点!  藏起来  快
Go! hide! come on.
快去藏起来
Just hide!
快  快  快走!
Come on. come on. let's go!
直升机在哪  就在那条路上
Where's the chopper? it's about a click back that way.
-你带工具箱了吗  -是的  就在这
Did you bring the kit? yeah, it's right here.
伙计  他看起来情况不妙  到底发生什么了
Jeez, man, he looks bad. what the hell happened?
少管闲事  是我们自己的事
You do your job. I'll do mine.
天快黑了  伙计
It's gettin' dark, man.
我们得马上离开
We gotta leave now.
Keamy先生  我们得回直升机那儿了
Mr. keamy, we gotta get back to the chopper.
Keamy  我们得回去了  因为我现在告诉你
Keamy, we gotta get back, cause I'll tell ya right now,
在晚上我可找不准法拉第方位
I am not flying faraday's bearings at night.
如果你还想回去  得马上离开  先生
So if you wanna get back, we gotta leave right now, sir.
好  你带路
Fine. you lead the way.
走
Come on.
好  走吧
Okay. come on.
保管好它
Watch it now.
帐篷搞定了  一切准备就绪
The tent's all set. everything's ready.
很好  谢谢
Good. thanks.
我这里还需要一个人帮忙
Listen, I could use an extra pair of hands in there.
-你可以帮我吗? -我...我想还是不要了
You wanna help me out? um, I don't... I don't think that's a good idea.
只不过是举个镜子
It's just holding a mirror.
Jack想看手术  "跟我说话"
Jack wants to watch the surgery, "talk me through it."
怎么了?
What?
只是有点吃惊
I'm just surprised
他怎么不现在就把那东西弄出来
He's not taking it out of himself by now.
你在干吗?
What are you doin'?
-不用拐杖我也可以走上50英尺 -我来扶你
I don't need a stretcher. I can walk 50 feet. I'll help you.
他们很快就会带着器具回来了
They're gonna be back with the instruments soon.
他们一回来我们就开始手术
We need to be ready to go as soon as they get back.
貌似我要做你的护士了
So it looks like I'm gonna be your nurse.
又不是第一次了
Wouldn't be the first time.
听着  呃...
Listen, um...
-如果我有什么三长两短 -闭嘴  Jack
If something happens to me-- shut up, Jack.
你好直接啊
Fair enough.
Kate?
醒醒  Kate
Wake up, Kate.
很晚了  我刚回来
It's late. I just got home.
工作到现在吗?
Were you working?
没  我...
No. i...
我只是...去买了点东西
I just... had to stop and get something.
花了些时间
It just took a while.
怎么啦?  出什么事了?
What's going on? what's wrong?
我给Aaron读故事的那天晚上
The other night, when I was reading to aaron,
你说...
You said...
那个我才是本来的我
That I was a natural.
你真的...
Do you really...
你真的认为我可以做得好吗?
Do you really think that I'm good at this?
当然
Yeah.
你可以的
You're good at this.
愿意嫁我吗?
Will you marry me?
我愿意
Yes.
我当然愿意  我愿意
Of course I will. yes.
看  他们回来了
Look, they're back.
东西都找到了吗?
Did you find everything?
是的  女士  单子上的都找到了
Yes, ma'am. entire list.
他还好吗?
Is he okay?
暂时还好  Sun  我们需要给这些东西消毒
For now. sun, we need to sterilize these.
那里有开水
There's a pot of water boiling over here.
什么事?
Yeah?
我知道你听得懂我说什么
I konw you understand me.
我知道你会说韩语
I know you speak Korean.
我和Sun谈论你的时候  你笑了
You smiled when Sun and I talked about you
在救护站你偷听我们说话了
And you were listening to us at the station
不好意思
I'm sorry.
也许我该找你妻子来翻译一下
Perhaps I can get your wife to translate--
如果你还不承认...
If you continue to lie...
你朋友Daniel会遭殃的
I'm going to hurt your friend Daniel.
我会把他的手指一个个折断
I'm going to break his fingers one at a time.
这下你听懂了吗?
Do you understand that?
你想要什么?
What do you want?
直升机来救你的时候...
When the helicopter comes for you...
带我妻子一起离开这里
You're going to take my wife off this island.
那你和你的其他朋友呢?
What about you and the rest of your friends?
只管带上她就行了
Just get her on the helicopter.
知道吗  Jack
You know, Jack,
他们在医疗站找到了些麻醉剂
They found some chloroform at the medical station.
我可以帮你全身麻醉
I could knock you out.
你不想梦到自己回家的美好画面吗?
Wouldn't you rather be dreaming about something nice back home?
不用了  给我局部麻醉就好了
No, I'll manage with the lidocaine.
把这个举在这里
Just hold it right there.
好了  现在我要麻醉手术部位
Okay, now this is gonna numb the area of the first incision.
之后  我会告诉你
After that, I would like to be able to tell you
你什么都感觉不到了  但...你能感觉到
You're not gonna feel a thing, but... you will.
准备好了吗?
You ready?
好了  开始
Okay. here we go.
很好  Jack  还有一刀
Okay, Jack. one more.
哦!  好  尽量别动
Oh! okay, try not to move.
安静得躺好
Just stay still.
-Spreader -Kate  我看不到
Spreader. Kate, i-i can't see it.
-抱歉 -别想着镜子了  别动  spreader
Sorry. don't worry about the mirror. just stay still. spreader.
很好  不错
That's good. that's good. yeah.
很好
That's good.
-给他全身麻醉  bernard -别  别
Knock him out, bernard. no! no. hey.
我不想失去意识
Not wanna be unconscious.
-你也不想情况失控吧 -Kate
You don't want to be out of control. Kate.
-Kate  你该离开  bernard -别走  Kate
Kate, you need to leave. bernard! no. Kate.
-Kate  你该离开  bernard快 -求你了  别
Kate, you need to go. bernard! please. no!
-Kate  快出去  bernard快点 -Kate...
Kate, get out of here! bernard. Kate...
-Jack -Kate
Jack. Kate.
Kate  给我出去!  bernard!  全身麻醉
Kate, get outta here! damn it, bernard! knock him out!
对不住了  Jack  我也觉得这样好些
I'm sorry, Jack, but I agree.
Ryan Laker
Laker, ryan.
男性  36岁
Patient is male, 36.
造骨细胞出现在
Osteoblastoma is present
腰椎下侧
In the posterior area of the lumbar.
建议进行活组织切片检查以...
I am recommending biopsy for...
Jack?
你还好吗?
You okay?
呃  是的  我...我...我没事
Uh, yeah. I'm--i'm... I'm okay.
我  呃...
I, uh...
我只是  呃...
I just, uh...
那个  烟雾探测器...
The, um, the smoke detector was...
一直响  我只是...
Was beeping, and I just...
好吧  谢谢你保护我们
Okay. thank you for keeping us safe.
Erika  呃...
Erika, um...
可以帮我个忙吗?
Do you mind doing me a favor?
好啊  当然
Yeah, sure.
可以给我开点...
Can you write a script for...
安眠药吗?
Clonazepam?
你要的?
For you?
是的  呃...我最近太忙了
Yeah, um... I just got a lot going on right now,
我只是有点透不过气来
And I'm just a little snowed under
病人太多了  我和Kate又订婚了
With all my caseload, and Kate and I got engaged.
就是...晚上觉不太好睡  你知道的  只是...
Just... not sleepin' very well at night, you know? just...
知道嘛  订婚
You know, getting engaged
该是让人轻松的事  而不是给人压力的
Is supposed to help reduce stress, not create it.
是的  没错
Yeah. you're right.
也许你该找个人聊聊
Maybe you should talk to someone.
晚安
Good night.
多待几小时
For an extra couple hours.
反正Jack从没在8点前回过家
Jack's never home before 8:00 anyway.
我至少能待一小时
I could stay for at least an hour.
我得挂了  Jack回来了  好的
I-i gotta go. Jack's home. Yeah, okay.
我再打给你  拜
I'll call you later. Bye.
嘿
Hey.
嘿  你吓到我了
Hey.You scared me.
不好意思  我以为你已经睡了
Sorry. I thought you'd be in bed.
是Noreen
That was Noreen.
是啊  我们经常一起带孩子去公园的
Yeah. She's one of the moms from the park.
什么?
What?
没什么  我只是...
Nothing. I just...
从没听你说起过
Never heard you mention her before.
那么现在你听到了
Well, now you have.
楼上见
I'll see you upstairs.
老爸?
Dad?
嘿
Hey.
她表现的不错
She did good.
她说你要是愿意可以进去
She said you could go back inside if you want to.
谢谢
Thank you.
好
Okay.
他没流太多血
He didn't lose that much blood.
我想我取出了阑尾
I got the appendix out
然后把一切归位
And put everything back where it belongs, I think.
那他没事了?
So he's gonna be okay?
他会好的
He should be fine.
我们还得说服他休息
We just have to talk him into resting.
希望我们好运
Good luck with that.
很抱歉我朝你大喊大叫
I'm sorry I yelled at you.
没关系
Don't worry about it.
你受的苦够多了
You had enough going on.
你知道  他亲了我
You know, he kissed me.
什么?
What?
那天  你从岛的另一边
The other day, when you came back
回来  Jack亲了我
From the other side of the island, Jack kissed me.
但那吻却不是给我的  是为他自己
But it wasn't for me. it was for him.
我坚信他是试着要证明些什么
I'm pretty sure he was trying to prove something.
什么?
Prove what?
他不爱别人
That he doesn't love someone else.
谢谢你  Juliet
Thank you, Juliet.
谢谢你救了他
Thank you for saving his life.
我知道你醒着
I know you're awake.
你提早回来了
You're home early.
Veronica人呢?
Where's Veronica?
我打发她回家了
I sent her home.
孩子睡了
The baby's asleep.
她为什么来这?
Why was she here?
什么?
Sorry?
女佣
The nanny.
她就工作到四点
She only works till 4:00.
我是六点到家的
I came home at 6:00.
有些事要办  所以...
I had to run some errands, so...
我要求她多留几个小时的
I asked her to stay a couple extra hours.
怎么了  Jack?
What's going on, Jack?
你怎么回来的那么早?
Why are you home so early?
我去见Hurley了
I went to see Hurley.
今天?
Today?
上周五
Last friday.
你怎么不告诉我?  我本该和你一起去的
Why didn't you tell me? I would've gone with you.
因为他疯了  Kate
Because he's crazy, Kate,
而我不想让你伤心
And I didn't wanna upset you.
你今天去哪了?
Where were you today?
我想让你...
I'm gonna ask you...
相信我
To trust me.
相信我  别管了
Trust me. Just leave it be.
你去哪了?
Where were you?
Jack  别
Jack, don't.
不  我昨晚听见你再打电话了
No, I heard you on the phone last night.
那是和谁说话?
Who were you talking to?
别问了
Just let it go.
-不  我想知道 -不  Jack
-No, no, I wanna know. -No, jack.
我想知道你去哪了  见谁了
I wanna know where you were. I wanna know who you were with.
那些都不要紧  Jack  求你
It doesn't matter, Jack. please.
不  告诉我  告诉我!
No, tell me. Tell me!
我在替他干活
I was doing something for him.
我答应过他
I made him a promise.
那...
It...
那没什么  那和我们俩没关系
It doesn't matter. It has nothing to do with us.
那你为什么不告诉我?
Then why won't you tell me?
因为--因为他不愿意让我说
Because--because he wouldn't want me to.
但他不在这  对吧?  不
But he's not here, is he? no.
不  他做了自己的选择
No, he made his choice.
他选择了留下
He chose to stay.
是我回来了
I'm the one who came back.
是我在这
I'm the one who's here.
是我救了你的命
I'm the one who saved you.
Jack
Jack.
你不能--你不能这么做
You can't-- you can't do this.
如果你有病就得去治病
If you have problems, you need to figure them out.
好吗?  因为我不能让这样的你接近我的儿子
All right? 'cause I can't have you like this around my son.
你的儿子?
Your son?
你甚至根本和他没有关系!
You're not even related to him!
嘿  小甜豆
Hey, sweet pea.
早安
Morning.
这会儿对中国人来说是太早了
It's way too early for chinese.
Claire呢?
Where's Claire?
去厕所了?
Ladies' room?
她就那么走进了丛林
She just walked off into the jungle.
什么时候?
When?
午夜  起来就走了
In the middle of the night. Just got up and left.
-你让她一个人? -她不是一个人
-You let her go alone? -She wasn't alone.
那和谁一起?
Well, who was she with?
她叫他"老爸"  我应该跟着他们
She called him "dad." I'd have followed them,
但我有禁令在身
But I have a restraining order.
没事了  没事了
It's okay. It's okay.
我在这
I've got you.
Claire!
==============| YYeTs字幕组招募启示 |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国) 双语字幕校正 时间轴调整
英语翻译 欧美影视新闻翻译 影视评论 论坛版主 美工人员
服务器提供者 发布宣传 联系地址：www.YYeTs.net
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====